http://www.usffab.com/usffab/privacy-policy/

Name
Email
Already a registered user?
click here
If you would like to register for full access to all site features
click here.
PRINT THIS PAGE
Your privacy is very important to us. Accordingly, we have developed this Policy in order for you to understand how we collect, use, communicate and disclose and make use of personal information. The following outlines our privacy policy.
Before or at the time of collecting personal information, we will identify the purposes for which information is being collected.
We will collect and use of personal information solely with the objective of fulfilling those purposes specified by us and for other compatible purposes, unless we obtain the consent of the individual concerned or as required by law.
We will only retain personal information as long as necessary for the fulfillment of those purposes.
We will collect personal information by lawful and fair means and, where appropriate, with the knowledge or consent of the individual concerned.
Personal data should be relevant to the purposes for which it is to be used, and, to the extent necessary for those purposes, should be accurate, complete, and up-to-date.
We will protect personal information by reasonable security safeguards against loss or theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification.
We will make readily available to customers information about our policies and practices relating to the management of personal information.
We are committed to conducting our business in accordance with these principles in order to ensure that the confidentiality of personal information is protected and maintained.
Contact Us
Login
Sitemap
Terms of Use
Privacy Policy
Copyright © 2020 Eagle Manufacturing Group.  All rights reserved.
Login
Username
Password
Remember Me
Register | Lost your password?
Register
Username
E-mail
First Name (required)Last Name (required)Company Name (required)Address 1 (required)Address 2City (required)State (required)Country (required)Zip (required)Day Phone (required) Please indicate that you agree to the
Terms of Service
(required)
A password will be e-mailed to you.
Log in | Lost your password?
Reset Password
Username or E-mail:
Log in| Register
Username or EmailPassword Forgot?  Register
Contact Us:
Please leave this field empty.
